const contest_3_1 = [
    {
        "S/N": 1,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Solve the equation for $x$ from the logarithmic equation",
        "Question": "$\\log _{6} x+\\log _{6} x^{2}=3$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$x=6$\n$\\left[\\log _{6} x+2 \\log _{6} x=3 \\log _{6} x=3, \\log _{6} x=1, x=6\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Logarithmic Equations", "Algebra"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 2,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Solve the equation for $x$ from the logarithmic equation",
        "Question": "$\\log _{3} x-\\log _{3}(x-1)=2$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$x=9 / 8$\n$\\left[\\log _{3}(x /(x-1))=2, x /(x-1)=9, x=9(x-1), 8 x=9, x=9 / 8\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Logarithmic Equations", "Algebra"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 3,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Solve the equation for $x$ from the logarithmic equation",
        "Question": "$\\log _{2} x=\\log _{2}(x+3)-1$",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$x=3$\n$\\left[\\log _{2}(x /(x+3))=\\log _{2}(1 / 2), x /(x+3)=1 / 2,2 x=x+3, x=3\\right]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Logarithmic Equations", "Algebra"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 4,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Distinguish between animal cells and plant cells with respect to the following",
        "Question": "Size and shape",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "The shape and sizes of animal cells vary greatly from irregular shapes to round shapes, most defined by the function they perform, whereas plant cells are similar in shape with most cells being rectangular or cube-shape",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology"
    },
    {
        "S/N": 5,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Distinguish between animal cells and plant cells with respect to the following",
        "Question": "Vacuoles",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Animal cells may have many small vacuoles, a lot smaller than the plant cells/ Plant cells have a large central vacuole that can occupy large portion of the cell's volume.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Cell Biology", "Cell Structure"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 6,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Distinguish between animal cells and plant cells with respect to the following",
        "Question": "Golgi bodies",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Animal cells have larger and fewer Golgi bodies, whereas plant cells have smaller but more Golgi bodies",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Cell Biology", "Cell Structure"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 7,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe oviparous animals with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Mode of reproduction",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Oviparous animals lay eggs that later hatch to form young ones.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Reproduction", "Animal Biology"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 8,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe oviparous animals with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Type of fertilization",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "Oviparous animals might undergo internal or external fertilization.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Reproduction", "Animal Biology"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 9,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Describe oviparous animals with respect to the following.",
        "Question": "Chance of survival of young ones",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "The chance of survival of the young ones is less as the eggs are laid in the environment where they are prone to various dangers",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Biology",
        "Topic Tag": ["Reproduction", "Animal Biology"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 10,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Define a base according to the Lewis concept:",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "A base is an electron pair donor.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Acid-Base Chemistry", "Lewis Theory"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 11,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Define an acid according to the Bronsted - Lowry concept",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "An acid is a proton donor.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Acid-Base Chemistry", "Bronsted-Lowry Theory"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 12,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "What are the usual constituents of a buffer solution?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "A buffer solution will usually contain a weak acid and its conjugate base or a weak base and its conjugate acid.",
        "calculations present": "No",
        "Subject": "Chemistry",
        "Topic Tag": ["Solutions", "Buffer Solutions"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 13,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "If the half-life of a first order reaction is 2.00 minutes, calculate the rate constant of the reaction.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\mathrm{t}_{1 / 2}=0.693 / \\mathrm{k}$\n$$\n\\mathrm{k}=0.693 / 2.00 * 60.0=5.78 * 10^{-3} \\mathrm{~s}^{-1}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry, Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Chemical Kinetics", "Rate Constants"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 14,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "The decay constant of a radioactive substance is $6.60^{*} 10^{-3} \\mathrm{~s}^{-1}$. Calculate the half life of the substance.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$\\mathrm{t}_{1 / 2}=0.693 / \\mathrm{k}$\n$$\n=0.693 / 6.60 * 10^{-3}=105 \\mathrm{~s} \\text { or } 1 \\min 45 \\mathrm{~s}\n$$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry, Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Radioactivity", "Decay Constants"]

    },
    {
        "S/N": 15,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "A radioactive substance has a half - life of 2.00 hours. What percentage of the initial activity will be left after 10.0 hours?",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "There are 5 half - lives in 10.0 hours.\nSo, the percentage left is $3.13 \\%$ of the initial activity.",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Chemistry, Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Radioactivity", "Half-life Calculations"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 16,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the magnitude of the normal force on a $15 \\mathrm{~kg}$ object at rest on a plane inclined at $30^{\\circ}$ to the horizontal.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$130 N$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Mechanics", "Normal Force"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 17,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the magnitude of the friction force on a $16 \\mathrm{~kg}$ object at rest on a plane inclined at $30^{\\circ}$ to the horizontal.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$80 \\mathrm{~N}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Mechanics", "Friction Force"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 18,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the magnitude of the normal force on a $24 \\mathrm{~kg}$ object at rest on a plane inclined at $60^{\\circ}$ to the horizontal.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$120 \\mathrm{~N}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Mechanics", "Normal Force"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 19,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the magnitude of the magnetic force on a $0.50 \\mathrm{~m}$ section of a straight conductor carrying a current of $2.0 \\mathrm{~A}$ that lies perpendicular to a uniform $0.60 \\mathrm{~T}$ magnetic field.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$0.60 \\mathrm{~N}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Electromagnetism", "Magnetic Force"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 20,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the magnitude of the magnetic force on a $0.40 \\mathrm{~m}$ section of a straight conductor carrying a current of $3.0 \\mathrm{~A}$ that makes an angle of $30^{\\circ}$ to a uniform $0.80 \\mathrm{~T}$ magnetic field.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$0.48 \\mathrm{~N}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Electromagnetism", "Magnetic Force"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 21,
        "Has Preamble": "No",
        "Preamble Text": null,
        "Question": "Find the magnitude of the magnetic force on a $0.50 \\mathrm{~m}$ section of a straight conductor carrying a current of $6.0 \\mathrm{~A}$ that makes an angle of $30^{\\circ}$ to a uniform $2.0 \\mathrm{~T}$ magnetic field.",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "$3.0 \\mathrm{~N}$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Physics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Electromagnetism", "Magnetic Force"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 22,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the equation of the locus of the point P (x, y) moving in the coordinate plane such that AP = BP given",
        "Question": "A(-4, 2) and B(2, - 4)",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "y = $x [(x + 4)^{2} + (y \u2013 2)^{2} = (x - 2)^{2} + (y + 4)^{2} , 8x \u2013 4y = -4x + 8y, y = x ]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Coordinate Geometry", "Locus"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 23,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the equation of the locus of the point P (x, y) moving in the coordinate plane such that AP = BP given",
        "Question": "A(3, -2) and B(2, - 3)",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "y = $-x [(x \u2013 3)^{2} + (y + 2)^{2} = (x \u2013 2)^{2} + (y + 3)^{2} , -6x + 4y = -4x + 6y, -2x = 2y, y = - x]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Coordinate Geometry", "Locus"]
    },
    {
        "S/N": 24,
        "Has Preamble": "Yes",
        "Preamble Text": "Find the equation of the locus of the point P (x, y) moving in the coordinate plane such that AP = BP given",
        "Question": "A(2, 4) and B (-2, -4)",
        "Question has figure": "No",
        "Question figure name": null,
        "Answer has figure": "No",
        "Answer figure name": null,
        "Answer": "y = $-x/2 [(x \u2013 2)^{2} + (y \u2013 4)^{2} = (x + 2)^{2} + (y + 4)^{2} , -4x \u2013 8y = 4x + 8y, 16y = -8x, y = -x/2]$",
        "calculations present": "Yes",
        "Subject": "Mathematics",
        "Topic Tag": ["Coordinate Geometry", "Locus"]
    }
]

export default contest_3_1